{
	"Hardy" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_darkbrown",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Calm" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_brown",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Brave" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_red",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Hasty" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_orangered",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Rash" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_orange",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Naive" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_yellow",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"QuickWitted" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_yellowgreen",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Docile" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_green",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Smart" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_mint",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Bold" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_sky",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Quiet" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_blue",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Adamant" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_navy",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Careful" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_black",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Bashful" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_whight",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Lax" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_pink",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Quirky" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_purple",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Dull" : {
		"back" : "aura_a_babyblue",
		"front" : "a"
	},
	"Serious" : {
		"back" : "aura_a_lapislazuli",
		"front" : "a"
	},
	"Fearful" : {
		"back" : "aura_a_mint",
		"front" : "a"
	},
	"Lonely" : {
		"back" : "aura_a_lavender",
		"front" : "a"
	},
	"Arrogant" : {
		"back" : "aura_a_red",
		"front" : "a"
	},
	"Charming" : {
		"back" : "aura_a_yellow",
		"front" : "a"
	},
	"Timid" : {
		"back" : "aura_a_orange",
		"front" : "a"
	},
	"Lovely" : {
		"back" : "aura_a_babypink",
		"front" : "a"
	},
	"Silent" : {
		"back" : "aura_a2_darkblue",
		"front" : "a2"
	},
	"Solitary" : {
		"back" : "aura_a2_warmgray",
		"front" : "a2"
	},
	"Dawn" : {
		"back" : "aura_a2_white",
		"front" : "a2_whitegold"
	},
	"Clumsy" : {
		"back" : "aura_a2_purple",
		"front" : "a2"
	},
	"Introvert" : {
		"back" : "aura_a2_red",
		"front" : "a2"
	},
	"Somber" : {
		"back" : "aura_a2_brown",
		"front" : "a2_copper"
	},
	"Cheerful" : {
		"back" : "aura_a2_orange",
		"front" : "a2"
	},
	"Curious" : {
		"back" : "aura_a2_green",
		"front" : "a2"
	},
	"Extroverted" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_prism",
		"front" : "aura_s_prism"
	},
	"Lousy" : {
		"back" : "aura_a_navypurple",
		"front" : "a3_purple"
	},
	"Meticulous" : {
		"back" : "aura_a_blacknavy",
		"front" : "a3_blue"
	},
	"Sociable" : {
		"back" : "aura_a_pastelpink",
		"front" : "a3_purple"
	},
	"Frail" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_blackgreen",
		"front" : "aura_s_blackgreen"
	},
	"Wild" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_blackred",
		"front" : "aura_s_blackred"
	},
	"Capable" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_bluelight",
		"front" : "aura_s_bluelight"
	},
	"Lunatic" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_purplelight",
		"front" : "aura_s_purplelight"
	},
	"Elegant" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_blackhole",
		"front" : "aura_s_star"
	},
	"Distracted" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_mint",
		"front" : "aura_s_champion2"
	},
	"Perfectionist" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_universe1",
		"front" : "aura_s_universe1"
	},
	"Immersed" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_universe2",
		"front" : "aura_s_universe2"
	},
	"Classy" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_pearl",
		"front" : "aura_s_pearl"
	},
	"Noble" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_star",
		"front" : "aura_s_star2"
	},
	"Pure" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_transparent",
		"front" : "aura_s_transparent"
	},
	"Neat" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_transparent3",
		"front" : "aura_s_star"
	},
	"BlueMoon" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_moon_blue",
		"front" : "aura_s_transparent_blue"
	},
	"FullMoon" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_moon_yellow",
		"front" : "aura_s_transparent_yellow"
	},
	"Spooky" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_halloween_a",
		"front" : "aura_s_halloween_a"
	},
	"Horrendous" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_halloween_b",
		"front" : "aura_s_halloween_b"
	},
	"BlueMoonFly" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_moon_blue_fly",
		"front" : "aura_s_transparent_blue_fly"
	},
	"FullMoonFly" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_moon_yellow_fly",
		"front" : "aura_s_transparent_yellow_fly"
	},
	"SpookyFly" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_halloween_a_fly",
		"front" : "aura_s_halloween_a"
	},
	"HorrendousFly" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_halloween_b_fly",
		"front" : "aura_s_halloween_b"
	},
	"Talented" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_game_a",
		"front" : "aura_s_game_a"
	},
	"Skilled" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_game_b",
		"front" : "aura_s_game_b"
	},
	"Honorable": {
		"back" : "aura_s_pvp_a",
		"front" : "aura_s_pvp_a"
	},
	"Glorious": {
		"back" : "aura_s_pvp_b",
		"front" : "aura_s_pvp_b"
	},
	"Baleful" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_dark",
		"front" : "aura_s_dark"
	},
	"Apocalyptic" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_end",
		"front" : "aura_s_end"
	},
	"Mystical" : {
		"back" : "aura_a2_greenmint",
		"front" : "a2_l"
	},
	"Unknown" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_universe3",
		"front" : "aura_s_universe3"
	},
	"Christmas" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_xmas_a",
		"front" : "aura_s_xmas_a"
	},
	"Affable" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_xmas_b",
		"front" : "aura_s_xmas_b"
	},
	"Wilderness" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_sunset",
		"front" : "aura_s_sunset"
	}
}